A Guide to the Additional Papers of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., ca. 1924-2003
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Public Activities: Appointment Books and Files
  - Speeches: American Association of Motor Vehicle Administrators, Williamsburg, Virginia 1984 Jul 16 (Box 40)
  - Speeches: Governor Robb's "Chuck Roast" 1984 Oct 8 (Box 40)
  - Speeches: Dedication of the Judicial Center, Winchester, Virginia 1984 Oct 20 (Box 40)
  - Speeches: Richmond Republican Gala 1984 Oct 26 (Box 40)
  - Speeches: Virginians for Reagan Campaign, Danville, Virginia 1984 Oct 31 (Box 40)
  - Speeches: Virginians for Reagan Campaign, Petersburg, Virginia 1984 Oct 31 (Box 40)
  - Speeches: Notes and Drafts n.d. (Box 40)
  - Statements by Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1965-1979 (Box 40)
- Series III: Personal, Family and Business Papers
  - Subseries A: Business Papers
    - Associated Press (2 folders) 1945-1952 (Box 41)
    - Daily News Record (9 folders) 1940-1952 (Box 41)
    - Daily News Record (14 folders) 1953-1977 (Box 42)
    - Daily News Record: Editor's Roundtable 1947 (Box 43)
    - Daily News Record: Notebooks 1986-1987, n.d. (Box 43)
    - Daily News Record: Readership Survey 1997 (Box 43)
    - Davenport & Company of Virginia, Inc. (3 folders) 1973-1977 (Box 43)
    - Farmers and Merchants National Bank and J.H. Yost (2 folders) 1945-1952 (Box 43)
    - H.F. Byrd, Inc. (3 folders) 1973-1976 (Box 43)
    - H.F. Byrd, Inc. 1977 Jan-May (Box 43)
    - H.F. Byrd, Inc. 1977 Jun-Dec (Box 44)
    - H.F. Byrd, Inc.- Transfers from Old Ledger Accounts (bound volume) ca. 1924-1951 (Box 44)
    - H.F. Byrd, Inc.- Transfers from Old Ledger Accounts (bound volume) ca. 1931-1951 (Box 44)
    - Taxes (4 folders) 1967-1977 (Box 45)
    - Winchester Evening Star (4 folders) 1938-1952 (Box 45)
    - Winchester Evening Star 1966 (Box 45)
    - Winchester Evening Star (3 folders) 1967-1968 (Box 46)
    - Winchester Evening Star (3 folders) 1973-1977 (Box 46)
    - Winchester Evening Star: Accounts Receivable (2 folders) 1946-1951 (Box 46)
    - Winchester Evening Star: Applications (2 folders) 1945-1947 (Box 46)
    - Winchester Evening Star: Applications 1948-1954 (Box 47)
    - Winchester Evening Star: Circulation Reports (2 folders) 1934-1949 (Box 47)
    - Winchester Evening Star: New Press (3 folders) 1945-1947, 1950 (Box 47)
    - Winchester Evening Star: Voice of the People File 1946-1981 (Box 47)
    - Winchester Evening Star: "Wastebasket File" (3 folders) 1949-1952 (Box 47)
  - Subseries B: Family and Personal Papers
    - Personal Papers (3 folders) 1971-1977 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Anniversary Celebration (30th) of Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. and Gretchen Bigelow Thomson Byrd, held at Skyland 1971 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Anniversary Celebration (40th) of Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. and Gretchen Bigelow Thomson Byrd, held at Mt. Vernon 1981 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Articles by Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1951-2003 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Awards and Certificates 1946-2003 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Awards and Certificates of Recognition, Honorary Degrees and Memberships, etc. (oversize) c. 1952-1984 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Bank Statements c. 1972-1980 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Gretchen Thomson Byrd Papers 1961-1987, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Personal: Byrd Family Miscellaneous 1930-1999, n.d. (Box 48)
    - Personal: Byrd Fellowship: Virginia Polytechnic Institute in Systems Engineering for members of the Naval Aviation Executive Institute 1975-1981 (Box 48)
    - Personal: Correspondence 1938-2002 (Box 49)
    - Personal: Correspondence: Family 1944-55, 1979-81 (Box 49)
    - Personal: Correspondence: University of Virginia and the Disposition of Senator Byrd's Papers 1977-2001 (Box 49)
    - Personal - Dividends 1955-1977 (Box 49)
    - Personal: Financial Disclosure and Federal Pay Raises 1967, 1978 (Box 49)
    - Personal: Miscellaneous, including political cartoon, poems, etc. (oversize) c. 1970-1985 (Box 49)
    - Personal: News clippings (2 folders) 1948-2003 (Box 49)
    - Personal: Newspapers Inserts featuring Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (oversize) c. 1966-1976 (Box 49)
    - Personal: License Plates belonging to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1978, n.d. (Box 49)
    - Personal: Patrol Bombing Squadron 13 History, with note by Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1998 (Box 49)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (8x10 Portraits) 1966-1970, n.d. (Box 49)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (chiefly 5x7 Portraits) 1966-1968, n.d. (Box 49)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Award Ceremonies, Presentations and Graduations c. 1966-2003 (Box 50)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. - Campaigning c. 1966-1976 (Box 50)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Family c. 1932-1989 (Box 50)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Groups of People (2 folders) c. 1966-1977, n.d. (Box 50)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Individuals (2 folders) c. 1967-1975, n.d. (Box 50)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Military Setting or Personnel (3 folders) c. 1967-1973, n.d. (Box 50)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Miscellaneous c. 1969-1985, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Personal: c. 1942-1975 (Box 51)
      Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Miscellaneous, including with Jim Baker, Associated Press Board of Directors, in his Senate office, with President Jerry Ford, with President Lyndon Johnson, World War II [Patrol Bombing Squadron ?]13 Ship's Crew, and New Jersey battleship (oversize)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Negatives 1967, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Notable Figures and Celebrities c. 1967-1978, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Notes c. 1964-1982 (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: with Presidents 1957-2000 (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: Speaking at Miscellaneous Events c. 1975-1979, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Jr.: U.S. Politicians c. 1966-1987 (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Sr.: Drawing, Portrait, and Statue 1927-1980, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Personal: Photographs of Harry F. Byrd, Sr., one with John Dalton as a boy (oversize) 1942, n.d. (Box 51)
    - Personal: Salute to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. for 10th Anniversary in Senate and Distinguished Public Service 1975, 1982 (Box 51)
    - Personal: Slides of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (2 folders) 1965, 1974-1981 (Box 51)
    - Personal: South Pole Trip (see also OS Box T-31 for flags taken on trip by Byrd) 1979 (Box 52)
    - Personal: "Unreconstructed Rebel: The Political Thought and Senate Career of Carter Glass, 1929-1936" Dissertation by Alfred Cash Koeniger (2 folders) 1980 May (Box 52)
- Series IV: Campaign and Political Papers
  - Subseries A: Campaign Papers
    - Campaign: Jack Anderson article controversy 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Announcement 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Announcement Letters (2 folders) 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Don Baldwin: June 29 Reception 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Tom Byrd 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Common Cause 1975-1977 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Computer Company 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Csaky and Warlick Advertising Inc. 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Edward S. De Bolt 1975-1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Direct Mail 1976 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: District Coordinators 1970 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Elections 1970-1974 (Box 52)
    - Campaign: Election Results 1970 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Engineers for Byrd 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Expenses and Contributors 1966 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Federal Election Commission 1977 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Federal Election Commission: Reports (2 folders) 1975-1977 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Finance Committee 1976-1977 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Finance Controversy: Gulf 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Finance: Gulf Depositions 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Form Letters 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Joseph C. Garnett 1976-1977 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Elmon Gray 1975 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Godwin Managers 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Mrs. Beverly B. Greenhalgh 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Linwood A. Holton 1974 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Law Information 1975 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Letters 1976 (Box 53)
    - Campaign: Mailing Lists 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Managers 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Managers - Letters 1975 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Harrison Mann 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Media 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Military Friends 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: J. Clifford Miller 1975-1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Lathan Mims 1974-1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Miscellaneous, including Buttons/Pins 1976, n.d. (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Miscellaneous Clippings 1974-1975 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Jim Olmstead 1975 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Organization 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Ann Dobie Peebles 1975-1977 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Martin Perper 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Petition Drive (4 folders) 1976 Feb-Jul (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Posters (oversize) c. 1966-1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Press List 1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Republicans for Byrd (1 of 2 folders) 1970-1976 (Box 54)
    - Campaign: Republicans for Byrd (2 of 2 folders) 1970-1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Secretary of State 1975 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Services 1973 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Paul Shuford 1975-1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: State Board of Elections 1975-1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Steering Committee 1970 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Surveys 1973-1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Lance Tarrance: Decision Making Info 1974-1977 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Telephone Survey 1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Testimonial Dinner (4 folders) 1975 Sep-1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Testimonial Dinner: Letters 1975 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: C.E. Thurston 1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: William M. Tuck 1976 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Virginians for Byrd 1975-1977 (Box 55)
    - Campaign: Virginians for Byrd: Contributions $100.00 and Under 1975 (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Virginians for Zumwalt: Contributions (4 folders) 1976 Jul-Oct (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Virginians for Zumwalt: Contributions Summaries 1976 Jul-Oct (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Virginians for Zumwalt: Expenditures 1976 (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Volunteers 1975-1976 (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Voting Record 1976 (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Voting Statistics 1977 (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Woltz and Associates 1976 (Box 56)
    - Campaign: Elmo Zumwalt 1976 (Box 57)
  - Subseries B: Political - 1976 Election
    - Political - 1976 Election -Campaign Contributions 1975-1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election - Campaign Contributions (Out of State): Alabama through Louisiana 1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election - Campaign Contributions (Out of State) -Maine through South Carolina 1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election - Campaign Contributions (Out of State): Texas through West Virginia 1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election - Campaign Contributions (Out of State): Ireland and Switzerland 1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election - Campaign Coverage 1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election - Campaign Pledges and Lawrence Langley (2 folders) 1976 (Box 57)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 1 (11 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 58)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 2 (3 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 58)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 3 (5 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 59)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 4 (6 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 59)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 5 (7 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 60)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 6 (6 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 60)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 7 (9 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 61)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 8 (3 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 61)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 9 (9 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 62)
    - Political - 1976 Election: District 10 (7 folders) 1975-1976 (Box 62)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Newspaper Articles (2 folders) 1976 Oct (Box 62)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Newspaper Articles (2 folders) 1976 Oct-Nov (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Martin Perper 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Report of Investigation of Voting Machine Set-up in Campbell County 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Speeches, Statements, and Memoranda 1975-1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Appearances 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Attacks on Byrd 1975-1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Biography 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Campaign Contributions 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Campaign Literature 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Jimmy Carter 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: CNO Performance 1974-1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Debates 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Defense 1975-1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Editorials 1975-1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt - Endorsements 1976 (Box 63)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Energy 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Foreign Affairs 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Issues 1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Kepone 1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Kissinger 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Labor Unions 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Military Friends for Byrd 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Miscellaneous 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt - Party Loyalty 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Republicans for Zumwalt 1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Strategic Arms Limitations Talks 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Ship Building 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Staff 1975-1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: Tax Reform 1976 (Box 64)
    - Political - 1976 Election: Elmo Zumwalt: U.S.S. Sanctuary Controversy 1976 (Box 64)
  - Subseries C: Political: Miscellaneous
    - Political: Combined Federal Campaign 1978 (Box 65)
    - Political: Democratic National Convention, Miami Beach, Florida Photograph Album 1972 Jul (Box 65)
    - Political: General Senate Information 1966-1976 (Box 65)
    - Political: Henry E. Howell (2 folders) 1968-1973 (Box 65)
    - Political: Issues: Ethics and Korean Influence 1977 (Box 65)
    - Political: Issues: Federal Budget c. 1938-1995 (Box 65)
    - Political: Issues: Federal Budget and the Department of Defense (2 folders) 1976 Apr 20 (Box 65)
    - Political: Issues: Federal Budget Notebook 1981-1982 (Box 65)
    - Political: Issues: New Hampshire Senate Race 1975 (Box 66)
    - Political: Legislative Activities (2 folders) 1977-1982 (Box 66)
    - Political: Magna Belts labeled "Ralph Andrews" n.d. (Box 66)
    - Political: Miscellaneous (2 folders) 1949-1989, n.d. (Box 66)
    - Political: Miscellaneous Campaign Articles, Polls, and Returns (2 folders) 1952-1978 (Box 66)
    - Political: Miscellaneous Newspaper Articles 1966-1972 (Box 66)
    - Political: 1966 Election Returns 1964-1966 (Box 67)
    - Political: 1968 Presidential Race 1968-1969 (Box 67)
    - Political: 1969 Senate Election Returns 1969 (Box 67)
    - Political: 1973 Campaign for Governor 1972-1973 (Box 67)
    - Political: Petitions for Reelection, Letters regarding 1982 (Box 67)
    - Political: Petitions for Reelection (3 of 9 folders) 1982 (Box 67)
    - Political: Petitions for Reelection (6 of 9 folders) 1982 (Box 68)
    - Political: Senate Race: Milton Colvin 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Race: Democratic Primary 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Race: Clive L. DuVal, Jr. 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Race: Ray L. Garland 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Race: Governor Linwood Holton 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Race: George Rawlings 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1981 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Close Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1973-1980 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senate Record Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. compiled by the Senate Democratic Policy Committee 1977, 1981 (Box 69)
    - Political: Senators' Wealth 1973-1980 (Box 69)
    - Political: Sponsorship and Co-sponsorship File by Subject (2 folders) 1966-1982 (Box 69)
    - Political: State Board of Elections Political Precinct Roster (oversize) 1973 Oct 5 (Box 69)
    - Political: Studies: "Political Involvement, Apathy, and Cynicism in the Congressional Elections of 1974" 1975 (Box 69)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Brief Survey of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1969 (Box 69)
    - Political: Surveys: "The Political Picture in the State of Virginia" 1970 (Box 69)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Political Survey Program to Provide U.S. Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. with Information on Voter Attitudes in the State of Virginia" 1975 (Box 69)
    - Political: Surveys: "The Six Factors Which Will Decide the 1976 Presidential Election" 1975 (Box 69)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Study of Attitudes of Virginia Voters" 1966 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Study of Attitudes of Virginia Voters" 1968 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Study of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1970 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Survey of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1966 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Survey of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1970 Jan (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Survey of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1970 Sep (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Survey of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1972 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Survey of the Political Climate in Virginia" 1973 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "A Survey Research Program for the Reelection of U.S. Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (2 folders) 1974 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: "The U.S. Senatorial Picture in the State of Virginia" 1970 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: The Virginia Poll 1981 (Box 70)
    - Political: Surveys: Virginians for Byrd Benchmark Survey 1976 (Box 70)
    - Political: G. Fred Switzer, Democratic National Committee 1948-1952 (Box 71)
    - Political: Virginia Election Returns 1968-1976 (Box 71)
    - Political: Virginians for Byrd Dinner Committee: Form Letters, News Releases, and Invitations 1982 Oct 16 (Box 71)
    - Political: Virginians for Byrd Dinner Committee: Mailing Lists (5 folders) 1982 (Box 71)
  - Subseries D: Political Notebooks
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (3 volumes) 1965-1967 (Box 72)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (3 volumes) 1968-1970 Part I (Box 73)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (3 volumes) 1970 Part II-1971 (Box 74)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (4 volumes) 1972-1973 (Box 75)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (4 volumes) 1974-1975 (Box 76)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (4 volumes) 1976-1977 Jun (Box 77)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (4 volumes) 1977 Jul-1978 Oct (Box 78)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (4 volumes) 1979-1980 (Box 79)
    - Senate Roll Call Votes of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. (4 volumes) 1981-1982 (Box 80)
    - Voting Record of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. by the Library of Congress Legislative Reference Service, arranged by date (1 volume) 1966-1970 (Box 80)
    - Voting Record of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., arranged by subject (5 volumes) 1966-1980 (Box 81)
- Series V: Plaques Awarded to Harry F. Byrd and Byrd Miscellany
  - Rhodesian Chrome Ore presented to Byrd in recognition of his repeated efforts which prevented the embargo on Rhodesian chrome 1971 (Box 82)
  - Guardian of Small Business 1973 (Box 82)
  - Two Fairfax County Little League signed baseballs n.d. (Box 82)
  - Unknown award featuring a figure giving a speech n.d. (Box 82)
  - Watchdog of the Treasury Award 1967-68, 1973-74 (Box 83)
    (2 awards)
  - Friendship Fire Engine Company 1971 Feb 15 (Box 83)
  - No. Va. Gama Speaking Award 1974 (Box 83)
  - National Bicentennial Medal Presented to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1976 (Box 84)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Coin 1981 (Box 84)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. Declared a Master Architect For his Generosity to the Masonic Home of Virginia 1991 (Box 84)
  - Special Forces Airborne Recognition n.d., (glass) (Box 84)
  - Naval Aviation Executive Institute Fellowship at V.P.I. in honor of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1975 (Box 85)
  - Bridgewater College n.d. (Box 85)
  - Chesapeake District of Civitan International Honors Harry F. Byrd, Jr. n.d. (Box 85)
  - United States Marine Corps n.d. (Box 85)
  - September Stated Communication Guest Speaker Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Berkley Lodge No. 167, Chesapeake, Virginia [1972] (Box 86)
  - Reserve Officers Association, Virginia Minuteman Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1979-1980 (Box 86)
  - Cuban People in Exile Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. for his efforts on behalf of a free Cuba 1975 Oct 10 (Box 86)
  - Presented to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. in Appreciation from the Dale City, Virginia, Nottingdale Residents for Service to the Community n.d. (Box 86)
  - Martinsville-Henry County Chamber of Commerce Appreciation to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. for 34 years of public service 1982 Jun 7 (Box 86)
  - Taxpayer's Responsibility Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1977 (Box 87)
  - "The Bird Bath" presented to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. by American Diabetes Association 1985 Sep 24 (Box 87)
  - University of Hartford Tax Institute 1979 Tax Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1979 (Box 87)
  - National Exchange Club Virginia District Distinguished Virginian Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1974 Jun 22 (Box 87)
  - The National Society of the Sons of the American Revolution presented the National Legislators Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1971 Oct 15 (Box 88)
  - National Taxpayers Union to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1973 Sep 19 (Box 88)
  - Virginia YAF Freedom's Award Dinner 1975 (Box 88)
  - The Sons of Confederate Veterans Recognition on efforts of Harry F. Byrd, Jr. in restoration of the citizenship of General Robert E. Lee 1976 Jan 18 (Box 88)
  - Disabled American Veterans Service Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. n.d. (Box 88)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr. Grand Marshall Saint Patrick's Day Parade, Richmond, Virginia 1985 Mar 17 (Box 89)
  - U.S.S. Shenandoah AD 44 presented to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1983 Dec 17 (Box 89)
  - Paul Carrington Chapter Sons of the American Revolution Distinguished Service Award to Harry F. Byrd, Jr. 1982 Feb 17 (Box 89)
  - In Appreciation Senator Harry F. Byrd, Jr. on Occasion of 350th Anniversary of Charles City County, Westover Plantation 1984 Oct 27 (Box 89)
  - The Tax Foundation 1973, (oversize) (Oversize Box S-76)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action Distinguished Service Award (oversize) 1977 (Oversize Box S-76)
  - Shenandoah Valley National Bank to Byrd Family of Virginia for 50 Years of Service (oversize) 1980 (Oversize Box S-76)
  - The Society of Fellows of Anti-Defamation League 1970 & 1972 (Oversize Box S-77)
  - Conservative Political Action Conference 1976 (Oversize Box S-77)
  - Barry M. Goldwater Scholarship Awards Dinner Chairman 1979 (Oversize Box S-77)
  - American Legion Distinguished Service Medal 1982 (Oversize Box S-77)
  - Virginia Farm Bureau 1982 (Oversize Box S-77)
  - U.S. Sixth Fleet Power for Peace n.d. (Oversize Box S-77)
  - Key from the Historic Appomattox Railroad Festival 1975 (Oversize Box S-78)